This is how you're going to get the
confidence to put your rates up.
Let's imagine a client pays you this
amount. This bit here
is going to be costs.
Even me making this video, this camera,
that camera, that guy,
this fucking studio, are costs.
Then I've got tax.
These aren't two sides. Then here,
let's say take-home.
If I want to give someone a discount,
I would have to say I take 10% off my
costs.
My tax reduces maybe a tiny bit.
My costs remain the same.
I'm really just eating into my flipping
take-home.
Whereas if you increase the amount
that you're charging someone,
your tax may be
a couple of percent. Your costs
are not going to change.
Whenever you put your rates up, it
is just extra money in your pocket.
The only place your prices can ever go
is up.
Now,
the only way you can put your rates up
is through demand.
The best lesson I can ever give you
is it's not the amount of degrees you got,
it's
not where you went to uni,
it's not how good-looking you are,
it's not the
socioeconomic state of the country,
it's not who's the President of the United
States,
it's not what's happening with Bitcoin
prices.
The thing that determines how much you
charge is the demand for your services